ZEESHAN ASIF

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+92 312 4072852

 \bowtie

zeeshanasif0007@gmail.com



Lahore

About Me

I am a professional front-end web developer with around three years of work experience. I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated person. I try to adapt myself to all working conditions and always try to give my best for my clients and the company I'm working with. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative.

Experience

Fiverr | 2021 - Present

Front-end developer

I started to provide my professional services to real clients around the world during this period. I have successfully completed all projects with 5-star ratings and exceptionally positive reviews.

• Fiverr Profile

Here are some projects I've done

- https://frombottomagency.com/
- https://marcocervetta.com/
- https://thinkcall.online/
- https://www.veeware.com/
- https://100startups.app/

Ping | Final Year Project

Minhaj University Lahore

I am developing an android app to do communication (send and receive text messages) via local network without needing any internet connection. The UI/ UX is much similar to the usual messaging apps. The app is being build using React Native. Objectives are

- Send and receive messages over local Wi-Fi network.
- Get notifications on getting any message.
- Manage app wide state using redux.
- Saving data on local storage.

JJ Maintenance | Jan 2023 - Present

Johnny & Jugnu

This is an android application "JJ Maintenance". The app is designed to manage and keep track of facility in the company. This project is also under production.

Objectives are

- Manage vendors.
- Generate tickets.
- Vendors get notification on ticket generation.
- Performing data operations using API.

Technology Stack

React JS

- Node JS
- React Native
- MySQL

Redux

Education

2019 - Present

Minhaj University Lahore

BSCS

I have completed 6 semesters and am currently enrolled in the 7th semester. My current GPA is 3.40. I gained a good knowledge of comparative studies here and improved my skills through this time.

2016 - 2018

Government College Gulberg

ICS

I always wanted to stay in line with computer sciences and so 2016 I began to study ICS in 2016 and completed it in 2018 at Government College Gulberg.

Core Technologies

- JavaScript (ES6+)
- Typescript
- HTML 5
- CSS 3 / SASS / SCSS

UI Frameworks

- Styled Components
- Tailwind CSS
- Material UI
- Chakra UI
- Bootstrap
- Framer Motion
- GSAP

Personal Skills

- Creative Thinker
- Imaginative
- Inovative
- Reliable
- Team Player

JS Frameworks & Libraries

- React JS
- React Native
- Next JS
- Alpine JS
- JQuery
- Redux
- Redux Toolkit
- Redux Thunk

Other Tools

- Github
- Vercel
- Netlify

Interests

- Web 3.0
- Node/Express JS
- Mongo DB
- Cyber Security
- Artificial Intelligence